{
  "title": "Intermediate to Advanced Japanese Phrases Challenge",
  "description": "Put your Japanese language skills to the test with this quiz featuring intermediate to advanced phrases. From nuanced greetings to expressions of gratitude and complex questions, each question provides options, a hint, and the correct answer in Japanese characters and Romaji. Challenge yourself and elevate your proficiency in Japanese!",
    "items": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How do you say 'Hello' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "こんにちは",
        "options": ["さようなら", "ありがとう", "すみません", "こんにちは"],
        "hint": "Common greeting"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'Thank you'?",
        "answer": "ありがとう",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "こんにちは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Expressing gratitude"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which word means 'Yes' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "はい",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "こんにちは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Affirmative response"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How do you say 'No' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "いいえ",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "こんにちは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Negative response"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is the morning greeting in Japanese?",
        "answer": "おはようございます",
        "options": ["こんばんは", "こんにちは", "おはようございます", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Morning greeting"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "How do you greet someone in the evening in Japanese?",
        "answer": "こんばんは",
        "options": ["おはようございます", "こんにちは", "こんばんは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Evening greeting"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What phrase is used to apologize or get someone's attention in Japanese?",
        "answer": "すみません",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "すみません", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Apology or seeking attention"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How do you ask 'How are you?' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "お元気ですか",
        "options": ["さようなら", "お元気ですか", "すみません", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Asking about well-being"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "How do you express appreciation for someone's hard work in Japanese?",
        "answer": "お疲れ様です",
        "options": ["はい", "お疲れ様です", "すみません", "こんにちは"],
        "hint": "Common expression in the workplace"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What question would you ask when you want to know what something is?",
        "answer": "これは何ですか",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "これは何ですか", "こんにちは"],
        "hint": "Asking about an object"
      }
    ]
  }
  